https://www.adaptivemall.com/privacy-policy-cookie-restriction-mode/

Our COVID-19 Response & Important Shipping Delays
FREE SHIPPING* on all orders | See Details
Menu
Need Help?
800-371-2778
CLOSE
StrollersStroller Style PushchairsAll-Terrain StrollersJogging StrollersBus or Van TransportCar Seat StrollersUmbrella Style StrollersLightweight Travel ChairsTilt-in-Space AND Reclining StrollersRecline ONLY StrollersTilt In Space ONLY StrollersUniversal AccessoriesStrollersStroller Style PushchairsAll-Terrain StrollersJogging StrollersBus or Van TransportCar Seat StrollersUmbrella Style StrollersLightweight Travel ChairsTilt-in-Space AND Reclining StrollersRecline ONLY StrollersTilt In Space ONLY StrollersUniversal AccessoriesShop All Strollers
Special Tomato
EIO Push Chair
Browse All Stroller Style Pushchairs
SeatingActive SittingCorner Chairs & TablesFloor SeatingHi Lo ChairsLoungers and Bean Bag ChairsMobile SeatingPortable SeatingRecline SeatingRecline and Tilt in Space SeatingSit-to-Stand StandersStationary SeatingSwingsTables and TraysTilt-in-Space SeatingSeating AccessoriesSeatingActive SittingCorner Chairs & TablesFloor SeatingHi Lo ChairsLoungers and Bean Bag ChairsMobile SeatingPortable SeatingRecline SeatingRecline and Tilt in Space SeatingSit-to-Stand StandersStationary SeatingSwingsTables and TraysTilt-in-Space SeatingSeating AccessoriesShop All Seating
Special TomatoSoft-Touch® Sitter
with Mobile Base
Browse All Mobile Seating
Car SeatsAirplane TravelBus TransportCar Seats & Special Needs TransportationCar SeatsAirplane TravelBus TransportCar Seats & Special Needs TransportationShop All Car Seats
Special Tomato
MPS Car Seat
Browse All Car Seats
BathroomToileting & CommodesBathingShoweringBath LiftBath TransferTransfer Shower ChairsBathroomToileting & CommodesBathingShoweringBath LiftBath TransferTransfer Shower ChairsShop All Bathroom
Columbia Medical
Hi-Back Toilet Support Systemwith Padding
Browse All Toileting / Commodes
Bikes & TrikesTricyclesBalance BikesFoot & Hand CyclesAdult BikesBikes & TrikesTricyclesBalance BikesFoot & Hand CyclesAdult BikesShop All Bikes & Trikes
Rifton Tricycle
Browse All Tricycles
MoreAdult Adaptive EquipmentAutismFine MotorFunGait TrainersGross MotorSleeping & Adaptive BedsStandersSwingsTables and TraysTherapeutic & Educational ToysTherapy SystemsUniversal AccessoriesWalkersMoreAdult Adaptive EquipmentAutismFine MotorFunGait TrainersGross MotorSleeping & Adaptive BedsStandersSwingsTables and TraysTherapeutic & Educational ToysTherapy SystemsUniversal AccessoriesWalkersShop All More
R82 Mustang
Browse All Gait Trainers
Special TomatoShop by NeedI Need Help SITTING...I Need Help STANDING...I Need Help With TRANSPORTATION...I Need Help WALKING...I Need Help in the BATHROOM...I Need Help LYING DOWNI Need Help With SENSORY INTEGRATION...I Need Help With BALANCE...I Need Help CRAWLINGI Need Help TALL KNEELING...I Need Help with FINE MOTOR SKILLS
EasyStandBantam
Browse All Sit-to-Stand Standers
Shop by NeedI Need Help SITTING...I Need Help STANDING...I Need Help With TRANSPORTATION...I Need Help WALKING...I Need Help in the BATHROOM...I Need Help LYING DOWNI Need Help With SENSORY INTEGRATION...I Need Help With BALANCE...I Need Help CRAWLINGI Need Help TALL KNEELING...I Need Help with FINE MOTOR SKILLSShop All Shop by Need
BrandsSpecial TomatoConvaid StrollersLeckeyRiftonInspired by DriveR82Columbia MedicalAdaptive StarAmTryke Special Needs TricyclesAquatec Bath LiftsBaby JoggerBeds by GeorgeBike USAbiliboCARES Child Aviation RestraintCoscoEasyStandergoErgoFreedom ConceptsGuidecraftHeadPod Head Support SystemIntegrity Custom ConceptsJensen SwingsKAYE Brand ProductsKeekaroo Brand ProductsKore StoolsLeggeroMaclarenMaking SenseMelissa & Doug Development ToysMeywalkOrmesaR.E.A.L. DesignRedbarn EnterprisesSafe Place BeddingSenseez Vibrating PillowsSmirthwaiteSpry Flo-Form® CushionsSTRIDER No-Pedal Balance BikesStokkeTherAdaptThomashilfenTriaid Special Needs TricyclesTumble FormsVibes Hi-Fidelity EarplugsYogibo Bean Bag Chairs & Accessories
See All Brands
Account
Login
About Us
Contact Us
Customer Care
FREE SHIPPING* on all orders | See Details
Account
Home
Privacy and Cookie Policy
Privacy and Cookie Policy
What we collect
We may collect the following information:
name
contact information including email address
demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers
For the exhaustive list of cookies we collect see the List of cookies we collect section.
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:
Internal record keeping.
We may use the information to improve our products and services.
We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
All Adaptivemall.com transactions are handled with industry-standard SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) encryption.
When you enter your credit card number into a Adaptivemall.com order form, it is transmitted across the Internet in an encrypted (scrambled) form, then decoded when it gets to us.
To check the security of your transfer connection, look at the lower left-hand corner of your browser window after accessing the server. If you see an unbroken key or a closed lock (depending upon your browser), then SSL is active. (You can also double-check by looking at the URL line of your browser. When accessing a secure server, the first characters of the site address will change from "http" to "https").
Some versions of browsers and some fire walls don't permit communication through secure servers. In that case, you'll be unable to connect to the server so you won't have to worry about mistakenly placing an order through an unsecured connection.
If you can't access the secure server for whatever reason, please place your order by phone, by US Mail or by fax.
Our Phone # is: Toll-Free 1-800-371-2778 (International #: 1-315-429-7112)
Our mailing address is:
Adaptivemall.com
Bergeron Health Care
15 Second Street
Dolgeville, NY
13329
Our 24 hour fax number is: 1-315-429-8862
If you are not the kind of person who worries about being hit by lightning as you're crossing the street, you probably don't have to worry that your credit card number will be intercepted on the way to a secure Web site. According to CNN, "The prevalent opinion...is that on-line credit card use is actually no riskier for consumers than traditional "low-tech" transactions."
We order products online all the time, both as a company and as individuals. When we use a credit card to buy something online, we feel at least as safe as we would using one in a store or restaurant.
Did you know that under the Fair Credit Billing Act, your bank cannot hold you liable for more than $50.00 of fraudulent charges? Should an unauthorized use of your credit card take place anywhere, anytime, you must notify your credit card provider in accordance with its reporting rules and procedures.
How we use cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling your personal information
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:
whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by letting us know using our Contact Us information
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please email us this request using our Contact Us information.
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
List of cookies we collect
The table below lists the cookies we collect and what information they store.
COOKIE nameCOOKIE Description
AMP_TOKEN
Contains a token that can be used to retrieve a Client ID from AMP Client ID service. Other possible values indicate opt-out, inflight request or an error retrieving a Client ID from AMP Client ID service.
CART
The association with your shopping cart.
CATEGORY_INFO
Stores the category info on the page, that allows to display pages more quickly.
COMPARE
The items that you have in the Compare Products list.
CUSTOMER
An encrypted version of your customer id with the store.
CUSTOMER_AUTH
An indicator if you are currently logged into the store.
CUSTOMER_INFO
An encrypted version of the customer group you belong to.
CUSTOMER_SEGMENT_IDS
Stores the Customer Segment ID
EXTERNAL_NO_CACHE
A flag, which indicates whether caching is disabled or not.
FORM_KEY
Stores form key used by page cache functionality.
FRONTEND
Your session ID on the server.
_ga
Used to distinguish users.
_gac_
Contains campaign related information for the user. If you have linked your Google Analytics and AdWords accounts, AdWords website conversion tags will read this cookie unless you opt-out.
_gaexp
Used to determine a user's inclusion in an experiment and the expiry of experiments a user has been included in.
_gat
Used to throttle request rate. If Google Analytics is deployed via Google Tag Manager, this cookie will be named _dc_gtm_.
_gid
Used to distinguish users.
GUEST-VIEW
Allows guests to edit their orders.
LAST_CATEGORY
The last category you visited.
LAST_PRODUCT
The most recent product you have viewed.
NEWMESSAGE
Indicates whether a new message has been received.
NO_CACHE
Indicates whether it is allowed to use cache.
PERSISTENT_SHOPPING_CART
A link to information about your cart and viewing history if you have asked the site.
RECENTLYCOMPARED
The items that you have recently compared.
STF
Information on products you have emailed to friends.
STORE
The store view or language you have selected.
USER_ALLOWED_SAVE_COOKIE
Indicates whether a customer allowed to use cookies.
__utma
Used to distinguish users and sessions. The cookie is created when the javascript library executes and no existing __utma cookies exists. The cookie is updated every time data is sent to Google Analytics.
__utmb
Used to determine new sessions/visits. The cookie is created when the javascript library executes and no existing __utmb cookies exists. The cookie is updated every time data is sent to Google Analytics.
__utmc
Not used in ga.js. Set for interoperability with urchin.js. Historically, this cookie operated in conjunction with the __utmb cookie to determine whether the user was in a new session/visit.
__utmt
Used to throttle request rate.
__utmv
Used to store visitor-level custom variable data. This cookie is created when a developer uses the _setCustomVar method with a visitor level custom variable. This cookie was also used for the deprecated _setVar method. The cookie is updated every time data is sent to Google Analytics.
__utmx
Used to determine a user's inclusion in an experiment.
__utmxx
Used to determine the expiry of experiments a user has been included in.
__utmz
Stores the traffic source or campaign that explains how the user reached your site. The cookie is created when the javascript library executes and is updated every time data is sent to Google Analytics.
VIEWED_PRODUCT_IDS
The products that you have recently viewed.
WISHLIST
An encrypted list of products added to your Wish List.
WISHLIST_CNT
The number of items in your Wish List.
